本字幕由 YYeTs人人影視 翻譯創作
歡迎愛好者加入我們  www.YYeTs.net
■
翻譯：         L.P(chongmei3250)
校對：還沒校對  監製：L.P(chongmei3250)  後期：L.P(chongmei3250)
嘿
Hey!
救命
Help!
救命  救命
Help! Help!
我操
Fuck.
好了 好了 好了
Okay, okay, okay. Okay.
號碼是多少  號碼是多少
Okay. What was it? What's the number? What's the number?
1  2  1...
1-2-1...
我艸
FUCK!
哪裏去了
Where is it?
-911  請稍等  -不  等一下  求你了
-MALE OPERATOR: 911. Please hold. -No! Wait! Please!
-你好  911  -你好 我被埋了
-FEMALE OPERATOR: Yes. 911. -Hello. I'm buried.
你必須救我 我不能呼吸了
You have to help me. You have to help me. I can't breathe.
-先生  -我被埋在了一個棺材裏  請救救我
-Sir? -I'm buried in a coffin. Please, help.
-請派人來找我 -請說慢點
-Send someone to find me. -Sin slow down.
-你的名字是什麼?  -保羅 保羅 康羅伊
-What is your name? -Paul. Paul Conroy.
好的  康羅伊先生你能告訴我你的位置嗎
Okay, Mn Conroy. Can you tell me your location?
我不知道我在一個棺材中
I don't know. I'm in a coffin.
我不知道在哪裏請救救我  我好害怕
I don't know where. Please, help. I'm scared.
-你在一個棺材中? -是的
-You're in a coffin? -Yes.
就像那種老式的  木質的棺材
It's like one of those old, wooden ones.
-你在殯儀館嗎?  -不 不 不
-Are you at a funeral home? -No. No. No.
我其實不知道
I don't know. No.
那你怎麼給我打電話?
(DISTORTED) How are you calling me right now?
什麼
What?
如果你被埋在棺材裏  那你從哪裏給我打電話
If you're buried in a coffin, where are you calling me from?
用手機  棺材裏有一個舊手機
From a cell phone. There was an old cell phone in the coffin.
-你用你的手機給我打電話?  -是的
-You're calling me from your cell phone? -Yes.
是的 是的不是 不是 這個不是我的手機
Yes. Yes. No, no. It's not my cell phone,
但是  我確實用手機給你打的電話
but, yes, I'm calling from a cell phone.
你爬進去棺材的時候裏面有個手機?
There was a cell phone in the coffin when you climbed in?
是的 什麼?
Yes. What?
-我沒有爬進來   -那你怎麼進去棺材的 先生
-I didn't climb in, though. -How did you end up in the coffin, sir?
-我是被放進來的 -在一個棺材裏?
-I was put here. -In the coffin?
是的  請救救我
Yes. Please, help.
-你說棺材是被埋了的? -是的
-And you're saying the coffin is buried? -Yes. Yeah.
我是一個卡車司機 我是一個美國人
I'm a truck driver. I'm an American.
這裏很熱 我不能呼吸了
It's hot in here, and I can't breathe.
-求求你了 -你知道你的位置嗎
-Please. -Do you know your location, sir?
-我告訴你了 在伊拉克的某地 請救我 -伊拉克?
-I told you, somewhere in Iraq. Please, help. -Iraq?
是的  我是一個卡車司機 一個美國人 為CRT工作
Yes. I'm a truck driver. I'm an American. I work for CRT.
-你是一個軍人嗎 先生 -不 你必須聽我說
-Are you a soldier; sir? -No, please, you have to listen to me.
我是一個卡車司機 一個美國人
I'm a truck driver. I'm an American.
我是一個在伊拉克工作的平民合同商我們在巴格達受到攻擊
I秉 a civilian contractor working in Iraq. We were attacked in Baqubah.
然後 他們開槍殺了他們
And they... They shot all of them.
-他們殺了誰? -其他司機
-They shot who, sir? -All of the other drivers.
你說這些都發生在伊拉克?那個國家?
And you are saying this happened in Iraq? The country?
是的  請認真聽我說
Yeah. Please, listen to me, okay? Listen to me.
他們給了我一個安全號碼在我錢包裏 但是現在我不知道哪去了
They gave me a safety number and it was in my wallet, and I don't know where it is now.
康羅伊先生 這裏是俄亥俄州的揚斯敦911
Mr Conroy this is 911 emergency in Youngstown, Ohio.
-俄亥俄州? -是的
-Ohio? -Yes, sir.
我不知道你是怎麼從另外一個國家打電話到這裏的
I'm not sure exactly how you called here if you're in another country but if you'd like,
如果你想要 我可以幫你轉接縣郡治安部
I can patch you through to the sheriff's department.
你不明白 算了
You don't understand. Forget it.
好的 好的 好的
Okay, okay, okay. Okay. Okay.
接電話 接電話
Pick up, pick up, pick up.
接電話
Pick up.
感謝致電康羅伊一家  我們現在不在家
SHANE: Thanks for calling the Conroys. We're not home right now.
請在B聲後留言 謝謝
Please leave a message after the beep. Thanks!
琳達 琳達 親愛的 是我
Yeah, Linda. Linda, honey, it's me.
我需要你馬上聯繫國民警衛隊
I need you... I need you... I need you to contact the National Guard right away,
或者五角大樓
or the Pentagon.
告訴他們我們在巴格達的迪亞拉省受到攻擊
Tell them that we were attacked in the Diyala province, in Baqubah.
他們需要找到我
They need to find me. Okay?
求求你 寶貝 你必須幫助他們找到我
Please, baby, you've got to help them find me.
-我是琳達 -不
-Hi, this is Linda. -No!
請留下你的口信 祝你有愉快的一天
Please leave a message. Thanks and have a great day.
琳達 琳達 我需要你馬上打電話給我
Linda! Linda, I need you to call me right away, okay?
打這個電話給我 萬分火急
Call me at this number. It's an absolute emergency.
打你手機上顯示的這個號碼 好嗎
Call me at the number that comes up on your screen right away. Okay?
我不知道他媽的到底發生了什麼 但是
I don't know what the hell is going on, but...
我被埋在了一個棺材裏
...I'm buried in a box.
I'm buried in a box.
我不能呼吸了
I can't breathe in here.
收到後請馬上打給我 求你了
Call me whenever you can. Please, baby.
哪個州哪個城市?
OPERATOR: What city and state, please?
我不知道 只要是FBI就行
I don't know. The FBI, wherever they are.
你想聯繫哪個指定的城市嗎?
Do you have a specific city you抎 like to be connected to?
隨便哪個都行只要是FBI就行
Anywhere. Any city. Just connect me to the FBI.
先生  可以幫你轉接的有波士頓
Sir; I have FBI Held of Hoes listed in Boston,
芝加哥  紐約  費城..
Chicago, New York, Philadelphia...
-無所謂 -紐黑文市的FBI
-It doesn't matter. -New Haven...
隨便哪個城市 只要幫我轉接 求你了
Any city, anywhere. Just connect me, please.
不好意思 先生 但是我們不能那麼做
I'm sorry, sir; but i'm not allowed to do that.
-芝加哥 行了吧 芝加哥 行嗎? -沒必要這麼生氣 先生
-Chicago! Fine? Chicago! Okay? -There's no need to be rude, sir.
請稍等
Please, hold for your number
你撥打的號碼
The number you requested...
3-1-2
4-2-1
6-7-0-0
要額外收取25美分的費用
can be connected for an additional charge of 25 cents
按1鍵
by pressing the number 1.
芝加哥辦公室 哈里斯特別探員
Chicago field office. Special Agent Harris.
-是聯邦調查局嗎? -是的 先生
-Is this the FBI? -Yes, it is, sir.
好的  我從伊拉克電話過來的
Okay. I'm calling from Iraq.
我被埋在了沙漠的某個地方 我需要你救我
I'm buried in the desert somewhere. I need you to help me.
哇哇 請說慢點
Whoa. Whoa. Sin slow down.
-你什麼時候在伊拉克? -現在
-When were you in Iraq? -Now.
我現在就在伊拉克 我是一個卡車司機
Now. I'm there now. I'm a truck driver.
我為CRT工作 我來這裏9個月了
I work for CRT. I've been here for nine months.
-請問你的名字是什麼? -保羅 康羅伊
-May I have your name, please, sir? -it's Paul Conroy.
保羅 康羅伊
Paul Conroy.
是
Yeah.
好的 保羅 跟我解釋下到底怎麼了
Okay Paul, explain to me what's going on.
好的 好的
All right, all right. Okay.
好的 我和另外一隊司機
All right, me and a convoy of other drivers
我們運送一些廚房用品去一個社區中心
were delivering some kitchen supplies to a community center.
然後有一群孩子 他們朝我們卡車上扔石頭
And then some kids, they started throwing rocks at the trucks.
然後 有個路邊炸彈在前面炸毀了其中一輛卡車
And then, an IED went off up ahead and it blew up one of the other trucks.
然後有一群人從屋子後面跑出來
And then these guys, they came out from behind the houses
他們開始朝著街上的人開槍
and they started shooting everyone right there on the street.
-你中槍了嗎? -我不知道
-Were you shot at? -I don't know.
我不知道 我在車隊的很後面
I don't know. I was way in the back of the convoy.
我猜我被人用石頭砸到了頭
I guess I got hit in the head by one of the other...
然後我昏迷了 這就是我最後記得的事
By one of the rocks and I blacked out, and that's the last thing that I remember.
然後我就在這個棺材醒來 被綁著
And then I woke up here, tied up, in a coffin.
-誰把你放在裏面? -我想應該是伏擊我們的那些人
-Who put you there? -I guess whoever ambushed us.
-一群小孩?  -不 不 不
-A bunch of kids? -No. No, no, no, no, no.
那些孩子 他們朝我們扔石頭
Some kids, the kids, they threw the rocks at us.
那幾個男人 應該是伊拉克人 或許是叛亂者 我他媽怎麼知道
These guys, some Iraqis, some insurgents. I don't fucking know.
他們突然跳出來就開始朝
They just... They popped out and they started shooting everybody...
-街上的人們掃射 -我想你說過他們沒有射到你
-right there on the street. -I thought you said they didn't shoot at you.
是沒有 他們殺了他們
They didn't! I don't know. They shot them!
不要再那裏大吵大喊了
Sin you're gonna have to stop shouting.
我會大喊大叫是因為你沒有認真聽我說
I'm shouting because you're not listening to me!
我需要你來救我
I need you to help me!
好的 好的 我明白了
Okay. Okay, okay. I got it.
你能跟蹤這個電話嗎?GPS之類的
Can you trace the call? GPS or something?
為什麼他們沒有開槍射你
Why is it that they didn't shoot you?
我不知道 我只知道他們沒有對我開槍
I don't know. I have no idea. They didn't. That's all I know.
你的社會保險號是多少 保羅
What's your social security number, Paul?
為什麼
Why?
什麼 誰在意這個
Why? Who cares?
我被埋在了沙漠中間
I'm buried in the middle of the fucking desert,
誰他媽還在意我的社保號是多少
who cares what my social security number is?
我是一個美國公民 派人過來救我
I'm an American citizen. Just send someone to find me. Please!
你知道你在哪裏...
Do you have any idea where...
什麼?等等  我聽不到你
What? Hold on, hold on. I can't hear you.
你說...等等...我不能...
What did you... Hold on, hold on. No, no, no. I can't...
操
Shit!
Fuck.
快
Come on.
歡迎致電克裏斯汀 羅蘭 湯瑪士公司
Thank you for calling Crestin, Roland and Thomas.
我能幫你轉接給誰?
How may I direct your call?
誰都行 我需要跟人說話
Somebody. I need to talk to somebody right away.
-這是緊急情況 -請問你是誰?
-It's an emergency. -Who is this, please?
我是保羅 康羅伊
It's Paul Conroy.
我是為你們工作的司機 我從伊拉克打電話來
I'm a driver for you guys. I'm calling from Iraq.
-我的車隊被襲擊了 -如果這是緊急情況
-My convoy was attacked. -Sin if this is a crisis situation,
你要撥打分配給你的安全號碼
you need to contact the safety number you were...
我知道 我知道
I know. I know. I know.
我沒有那個號碼 那群人把它拿走了
I don't have it anymore. The people took it.
誰拿走了?
Who took it, sir?
我不知道 我想是伊拉克人  我昏過去了
I don't... I don't know. The Iraqis, I think. I blacked out.
我將把你的電話轉給阿蘭 達文普
I'm going to ,out you through to Alan Davenport.
-那是誰? -人事主管 請稍等
-Who's that? -Director of personnel. Please hold.
人事?不 不 不 請等等
Personnel? No, no, no, no! Wait, wait, wait!
在CRT公司  我們和顧客一起工作
At CRT, we work with our clients
為他們在快速增長的全球經濟遇見的挑戰
to provide effective and sustainable solutions
提供有效的和可持續的解決辦法
to the challenges they face in our fast-growing, global economy.
你撥打的是克裏斯汀 羅蘭 湯瑪士公司
You've reached Alan Davenport,
人事部主管 阿蘭 達文普
Personnel Director at Crestin, Roland and Thomas.
請在B聲後留下你的名字和電話
Please leave your name and number at the tone,
我會盡快給你回電
and I will return your call as soon as possible.
我是保羅 康羅伊 我來自密歇根州的黑斯廷斯
This is Paul Conroy. I'm from Hastings, Michigan.
我是CRT公司的司機
I'm a driver for CRT.
我的車隊被恐怖分子還是叛亂者伏擊了
My convoy was ambushed by terrorists, or insurgents. I don't know.
我不知道是誰 我被困住了
I don't know who it was. And I'm stuck.
我被埋在地下的一個棺材裏 我需要幫助
I'm buried in a coffin in the ground, and I need help.
求求你派人過來救我
Please send help. I'm begging you.
我想我在迪亞拉省巴格達附近
I think I'm in Baqubah in the Diyala province.
我不大清楚 請馬上派人過來救我
I'm not sure. Please. Please send help right away.
我不能呼吸了
I can't breathe in here. I can't breathe.
我不知道我還能打給誰 請救...
I didn't know who else to call. Please, send...
操 我操
Fuck! Fuck!
我操
FUCK!
快
Come on.
喂 有人在嗎
Hello? Is anybody there?
喂
Hello?
-喂?-呼吸還是不呼吸  美國人?
-Hello? -JABIR: Breathe no breathe, American?
-呼吸還是不呼吸? -等等
-Breathe no breathe? -Wait, wait. Hold... Hold on.
我不知道你在說什麼 你是誰
I don't know what you're saying. Who is this?
美國人能呼吸還是能不呼吸?
American can breathe no breathe?
我不能呼吸 請把我弄出去
No, I can't breathe. Please get me out of here.
-出去? -是 是 讓我出去
-Get out? -Yeah, yeah. Get me out.
讓我出去 救救我
Get me out. Please help.
-軍人 -不 不 我不是軍人
-Soldier -No, no. I'm not a soldier.
我是一個卡車司機 只是一個合同商而已
I'm a truck driver. Just a contractor.
-合同商? -是 合同商
-Contractor? -Yeah, yeah, a contractor.
就這樣 不是軍人
That's all. No soldier.
-布萊克沃特 -不 不是布萊克沃特
-Blackwater -No. Not for Blackwater.
我不是安保合同商 我只是一個卡車司機
I'm not a security contractor. I'm just a truck driver. That's all.
-你是美國人? -是的
-You American? -Yeah.
那就是軍人
Then you soldier
不 我不是
No, I'm not.
我們沒有武器 但是你們仍然向我們開槍
I'm here, unarmed. But you still shot at us.
你們的頭和喉嚨 所以不要再說謊了
In head and in throat, so you tell no more lies.
不 我們沒有說謊 我們全都是司機
No, I'm not lying. We were all drivers.
-什麼司機? -卡車 卡車司機
-Drive what? -Trucks. Trucks.
那些裝滿補給品的卡車
The trucks you see driving around with supplies.
那就是我 就是我們 我們不是軍人 只是卡車司機
That's me. That's us. That's all. Not a soldier. Truck driver.
-五百萬 錢 -什麼?
-Five million, money. -What?
今晚9點給我五百萬 否則你就像狗一樣埋在那裏
Five million, money tonight, 9:00 p.m., or you stay. Buried like dog.
-五百萬美金  找誰要? -你家庭
-$5 million? From who? -Your family.
我家人沒有五百萬 如果他們有 我就不會在這裏了
My family doesn't have $5 million. If they did, I wouldn't be here.
從美國大使館要
From embassy.
是是是 從大使館要
I don't know. Yeah, yeah, from the embassy.
如果你讓我從這裏出來 他們會給你錢
If you let me out of here, they'll pay you the money. Yeah.
今晚9點 五百萬
9:00 p.m., five million, money.
天啊 你的號碼是多少
Oh, God. What's your number?
-哪個城市? -密歇根州哈斯廷斯
-OPERATOR: What city and listing, please? -Hastings, Michigan.
我找多納 米切爾
I'm looking for Donna Mitchell.
這裏有兩個多納 米切爾
I have two Donna Mitchells, sir.
一個在聯邦路 一個在阿德摩爾林蔭道
One on Federal Road and one on Ardmore Avenue.
阿德摩爾林蔭道 我想是這個 不  操
Ardmore Avenue. I think. No. Shit!
我不知道 就給我那個吧
I don't know. Yeah, just give me that one.
-阿德摩爾林蔭道? -是的 阿德摩爾林蔭道
-Ardmore Avenue? -Yes, Ardmore Avenue.
請記住你要的號碼
Please hold for your number
你撥打的號碼...
The number you requested...
269-148
1998 馬上...
1998 can be...
快
Come on.
人呢
Where is everybody?
-你好? -多納 我是保羅
-DONNA: Hello? -Donna, it's Paul.
-嘿 最近怎樣 -還好
-Hey. How's it going? -Okay.
我想要跟琳達說話 她沒有接我的電話
I need to talk to Linda. She's not answering her phone.
我遇見難題了
I've got a problem.
我被一群人抓住為人質了
I've been held hostage by a group of guys that...
騙你的 我其實不在家
Fooled you. I'm not really home.
但是如果你留下口信 我會盡快給你回電 拜拜
But if you leave a message, i'll get back to you as soon as I get in. Bye-bye.
多納 我需要跟琳達說話 情況萬分火急
Donna, I need to talk to Linda. It's an absolute emergency.
讓她打給我 用來電顯示的號碼
Have her call me. Use star 69 to find out the number of this phone
然後讓她打給我 好嗎
and have her call me at this number, okay?
-保羅? -多納
-DONNA: Paul? -Donna.
-你想要什麼? -我需要跟琳達說話 她在哪裏
-What do you want? -I need to talk to Linda. Where is she?
我不知道 我一天沒和他說話了 打她手機試試
I don't know. I haven 't talked to her all day. Call her cell. ..
-你在你電腦邊嗎? -是的 怎麼了
-Are you at your computer right now? -Yeah. Why?
好 我需要你幫我找個政府部門的號碼
Okay, I need you to look up a number for me to the State Department.
保羅 我正要去超市 我真的...
Paul, I was just heading out to the supermarket. I really...
求你了 就幫我找個電話號碼
Please, please, please. Just look up the number for me.
-一切都好嗎? -不 一切都不好
-ls everything all right? -No! Everything is not all right!
-就幫我找個電話號碼 -不要對我喊叫
-Just look up the number for me. -Don 't fucking yell at me...
-我沒有對你喊叫 多納 -不 你有
-I'm not yelling at you, Donna. -Yes, you are.
不 我沒有 快給我他媽的電話號碼
No, I'm not. Just get me the fucking number!
給我電話號碼 給我他媽的電話號碼
Get me the number! Get me the fucking number!
操
FUCK!
你他媽的婊子
You stupid fucking cunt!
操
FUCK!
操  婊子
Fuck you, bitch! Fuck you!
操
Fuck you!
-什麼? -多納 我真的很抱歉我對你喊叫
-DONNA: What? -Donna, I'm very sorry that I yelled at you.
我不應該這麼做
I shouldn't have done that.
我最後求你一次給我那個電話號碼
But I'm only going to ask you one more time to get me this number,
否則 我會死的
and if you don't, I'm gonna die.
-什麼? -求求你 我沒有時間解釋了
-What? -Please, I don't have time to explain.
-那個號碼 -好吧 等等
-The number. -Okay, hold on.
-好 政府部門 -是的
-Okay. State Department. -Yeah .
-202 -202
-It's 202... -202.
-134... -134.
-4 750. -4750?
-好了 -好的 去死吧
-Yeah. -Okay. Fuck you.
美國政府
MAN: United States Department of State.
我是一個在伊拉克工作的美國公民 我被綁架了
I'm an American citizen, working in Iraq. I've been taken hostage.
-我需要跟某人談談 -你從哪裏打電話來 先生
-I need to speak to someone right away. -Where are you calling from, sir?
從伊拉克 我是一個卡車司機
From Iraq. I'm a truck driver.
為克裏斯汀 羅蘭 湯瑪士公司工作
I work for CRT. Crestin, Roland and Thomas.
我的車隊被襲擊了然後我被抓住了
My convoy was attacked and I'm being held for ransom.
-綁匪跟你在一起嗎? -不 我被埋在某個地方
-Are the kidnappers with you? -No. I'm buried somewhere.
-你被埋了? -是的 在一個棺材裏
-You're buried? -Yeah. Yeah, in a coffin.
這是一個木製的箱子 一個老式的木製棺材
It's a wooden box, an old wooden coffin.
你有嘗試聯繫外面的軍隊嗎?
Did you try contacting the military out there?
他們給了一個安全號碼給我
They gave me a number to call, a safety number.
-但是綁匪拿走了 -他們挾持你為人質?
-But the people took it. -The people holding you hostage?
-是的 是的 -我不知道
-Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. -I don't know.
-稍等 我幫你轉接....-不 不要讓我等
-Hold on. Let me connect you... -No, don't put me on hold! No!
-麗貝卡 布朗寧 -你好?
-Rebecca Browning. -Hello?
你好 我剛被告知你的情況
Yes, hello. I was just informed of your situation.
是的 我的情況
Yeah, my situation.
我快沒有時間了 但是你們的人一直讓我等
I'm running out of time and you guys keep putting me on hold.
-你他媽怎麼了 -對不起
-What the hell is wrong with you? -I'm sorry.
不要道歉 救我
Don't be sorry. Just help me.
我有幾個問題想問你 康羅伊先生
I just have a few questions for you, Mn Conroy.
-你肯定在開玩笑 -瞭解這些信息對我們
-You've got to be kidding me. -it's important that I get this information.
-對我們營救你非常重要  -等等
-It抣l help make a rescue attempt... -Wait, wait. Hold on, hold on. Wait, wait.
-你怎麼知道我的名字? -什麼?
-How do you know my name? -I'm sorry?
我的名字 我沒有告訴你 我也沒有告訴那個男人
My name, I didn't give it to you. I didn't give it to the other guy either.
到底是怎麼了
What's going on right now?
我們收到了CRT公司代表的電話 你給他留了口信?
We received a call from a representative at CRT. You left him a message?
-是的 -他馬上聯繫了我們
-Yeah? -He contacted us right away.
所以你知道怎麼回事吧
So if you know what the hell is going on,
那你們做了什麼來救我出去
then what have you done to get me out of here?
我們從華盛頓能做到的不多
Well, there 's little we can do from Washington.
那只能這樣了?因為你能做的不多
So that's it? I'm just supposed to sit here and rot
我只能在這裏等著腐爛而死?
because there's little you can do?
-不是的 -那怎樣?
-No. -Then what?
我需要知道你的車隊在何時何地被伏擊
I need to know where you were when your convoy was ambushed.
-在迪亞拉省的巴格達 -好的
-In Baqubah, in the Diyala province. -Okay.
綁匪有和你聯繫嗎
And has contact been made with the kidnappers?
有 他們說今晚9點前要500萬美金
Yeah. The guy says he wants $5 million by 9:00 tonight.
好的   然後呢...
Okay or else...
然後他會帶我去海洋世界
Or else he'll take me to SeaWorld.
-你他媽到底在想什麼  小姐 -我們會盡我們最大的努力
-What the hell do you think, lady? -We'll do everything we can.
那你們會付款嗎?
So you'll pay them then? Yeah?
-不 我們不能那麼做 -等等 為什麼
-No. That we can't do. -Wait, wait. Why?
這是美國政府的政策
It's the policy of the United States government
永遠不跟恐怖分子談判
to not negotiate with terrorists.
不要跟我講美國政府的政策
Not the policy of the United States government?
小姐 求你了
Lady, come on!
你坐在有空調的辦公室裏 你說的簡單
You're sitting in an air conditioned office, this is easy for you to say.
你不是那個被困在棺材裏埋在沙漠中央的那個人
You're not the one stuck in a coffin, buried in the goddamn desert!
-我理解你的沮喪...-沮喪?
-I understand your frustration... -Frustration?
小姐 我他媽會死在這裏 你明白嗎?
Lady, I'm going to fucking die in here. Understand that?
-喂? -我在
-Hello? -I'm here.
那就說點什麼 告訴我你怎麼讓我離開這裏
Then say something. Tell me how you can get me out of here.
好的
Okay.
你的電話號碼多少
What's the number on the phone that you're calling from?
-我不知道 你那邊沒有顯示嗎?-沒有 這邊顯示保密
-I don't Know. Did it come up on your end? -No. it's listed as unavailable.
告訴我 你記得電話號碼嗎
Tell me this, can you remember a number?
是的 我有 我有一條鉛筆
Yeah. No. I have a... I have a pencil.
-寫下這個 -好的 等等
-Okay write this down. -Okay, just a sec.
好的 繼續
Okay. Go ahead.
-410 -好
-410... -Yeah.
...195...
-5453. -5453.
-那是誰?-那是丹 布倫娜
-Who's that? -That's Dan Brenner
他是伊拉克人質解救小組的指揮官
He's the commander of the hostage working group over in Iraq.
人質解救小組?
Hostage working group?
在2004年成立來解決類似你這樣處境的人
Formed it in 2004 to deal with situations such as yours.
處境我喜歡你這樣描述
Situations. I love how you keep calling it that.
-你有記下來嗎? -有
-Did you write down the number? -Yeah.
好的  請稍等 我會將你轉接給他
Good. Now, just hold on, I 'll connect you with him now.
-他應該在等你電話會 -新聞媒體怎樣 我想打給他們
-He should be expecting you. -What about the news? I wanna call them.
不 不要打給媒體
No, don't call the news.
-我重複 不要聯繫新聞媒體 -為什麼
-I repeat, do not contact the news. -Why?
-這只會讓情況更加糟糕 -屁話
-It will only complicate things further.. -That's bullshit.
-你只是想掩蓋你們的不作為 -不 我只是為了保護你
-You're just covering your own ass. -No, I'm covering yours.
你不去找某樣東西 你就不知道它不見了
You don't go looking for something you don't know is missing.
每個人都需要知道我到底怎樣了
Everyone who needs to know about this does.
-我需要一切幫助 -我們快沒時間了 保羅
-I need all the help I can get. -We are running out of time, Paul.
所以你要馬上聯繫丹 布倫娜
That's why you need to contact Dan Brenner right away.
好
Fine.
我馬上轉接你
I'm transferring you now.
-布倫娜 -丹 布倫娜?
-Brenner -Dan Brenner?
-是保羅 康羅伊嗎? -是的 我是保羅
-ls this Paul Conroy? -Yeah, yeah, it's me. It's Paul.
保羅 我剛被告知你的情況
Paul, I was informed of what's going on.
我希望你知道我們早已經正在想法救你了
I want you to know that we're already working on trying to get you out of there.
謝謝 上帝
Thank you, God.
我被告知截止時間是今晚9點 對嗎?
I was told that we have until 9:00 p. m. ls that right?
-那就是綁匪說的 -好的
-That's what he said. -All right.
我們的時間不多
That doesn't give us a whole lot of time.
那些綁匪把你埋在了地下?
And just so I have this right, the kidnappers buried you in the ground?
是的 是一個老的木製棺材
Yeah. It's an old, wooden coffin.
所以我猜你的手機能夠收到信號
Okay my guess is that since you're able to get a cell signal,
-你被埋的應該只有幾尺深而已 -是啊 我不知道 應該是吧
-you're no more than a few feet underground. -Yeah, I don't know. Maybe.
你的手機電量怎樣?還能維持多長時間
What about battery life? How much does the phone have left?
-隻剩下一半了 -好的 你必須省著點用
-It's just less than half. -Okay you have to conserve that battery.
我們最大的希望是通過跟蹤你的手機找到你
Our best bet of finding you by tracking your cell signal.
-鈴聲是設置在響鈴還是震動狀態? -震動
-ls the ringer set on a sound or vibrate? -Vibrate.
我需要你按住*號鍵不放
I need you to press and hold down the asterisk key
轉為響鈴狀態 這樣比較節約電
to change it to a ring tone. It will use less power
-那我的zippo呢?-你有一個打火機?
-What about my Zippo? -You have a lighter?
-是的 -用它來找找附近的標記
-Yeah. -Use it to look around for markings,
商標之類的 -這會燃燒掉氧氣嗎?
logo, whatever you can find. -Won't it use up oxygen?
現在不用擔心這個 試試找找
Don 't worry about that now. Just try to find...
-沒有打火機這裏好暗好暗 -我理解 保羅
-It's just so dark in here without it. -I understand, Paul.
試試找出能夠象徵棺材產地的標記
Try to find anything in there that might indicate where that coffin was made.
-你們要盡快 -我們已經在盡我們最大的努力了 保羅
-You guys have to hurry. -We're working as fast as we can, Paul.
你知道還有生還者嗎?
Do you Know if there were any other survivors?
-你的車隊的人嗎? -是的
-From your convoy? -Yeah .
這點還不清楚
Still unclear at this point.
我僅僅只是想做些對我家庭有用的事
I just wanted to do right by my family. That's all.
我不知道會發生今天這樣的事
I didn't know it was going to be like this out here.
我想沒人能預料到
I don't think any of us did.
-是他 他打來了 -綁匪?
-That's him. He's calling. -The kidnapper?
-是的 我該怎麼辦 -你知道他的號碼?
-Yeah. What should I do? -You know his number?
-是的 -給我
-Yeah. -Give it to me.
-好的  那這通電話怎麼辦 -先給我電話號碼
-Okay. What about the call? -Give me the number first.
-他要掛掉了 -接電話
-He's going to hang up. -Take the call.
-我...好吧  -沒事 接電話
-I... Okay. -That's okay, just take the call.
喂  喂
Hello! Hello.
2小時4分鐘
JABIR: Two hour; four minute.
-你需要給我多點時間  -你跟大使館說了嗎
-You have to give me more time. -You talk to embassy?
-給錢? -是的 我跟其他人說了
-Give the money? -Yeah, yeah. I talked to someone.
政府說他們不會付錢
The government. They said that they won't pay the money.
-不給錢?  -不給
-No pay? -No.
他們說不和恐怖分子談判
They said they don't negotiate with terrorists.
恐怖分子?我是恐怖分子?
Terrorists? I am terrorist?
是的 你是恐怖分子 你就是個兔崽子
Yeah. Yeah. You're a terrorist, you son of a bitch.
你害怕了   所以我就是恐怖分子?
You terrified, so I am terrorist?
我對你做了什麼
What did I ever do to you?
-做了什麼? -是啊
-Ever do? -Yeah.
我來這裏是因為工作 我要賺錢
Yeah. I'm here because it's a job, to make money.
-就這樣 -你來之前我有工作
-That's it. -I have job until you come.
-現在我的家庭什麼都沒有了 -那不是我的錯
-Now my family have nothing. -That's not my fault!
911不是我的錯  但是你們來了
9/11 was not my fault, but you still here.
薩達姆不是我的錯 你們又來了
Saddam was not my fault, but you still here.
我告訴過你 我來這裏是為了工作  是幫助重建
I told you, I'm only here to work. To help rebuild.
重建你們破壞掉的
Rebuild what you destroyed.
停下來吧 求你了 我僅僅是一個卡車司機而已
Stop! Stop! Just please, stop! I'm just a guy. I'm just a truck driver. Okay?
我沒有權力做任何決定
I'm nobody that makes decisions about anything.
我只是想回家
I just want to go home.
喂?
Hello?
-你拍視頻 要求贖金視頻 -好 好
-You make video. Ransom video. -Yeah, yeah!
如果你讓我走  我會拍個視頻
I'll make a video. If you let me go, I'll make a video.
不 你現在就拍
No. You make video now.
-什麼?現在?  -用手機攝像頭
-What? How? -Use video on phone.
紙條在你腳邊
Near foot. You read note near foot in box.
-我沒看到 -在你腳邊
-I don't see it. -Near foot.
-從盒子裏面念紙條內容 -好的 好的
-Read note inside box. -Okay, okay.
-如果我拍了視頻 你們讓我走?  -除非我們收到了錢
-If I make the video, you let me go? -Only if we get money.
沒人會為了我給這500萬美金的
Nobody's going to pay $5 million for me.
那我們拿少點 100萬
We take less. One million, money.
如果他們付錢 你會讓我走?
If they pay, you'll let me go?
100萬
One million, money.
感謝致電康羅伊一家  我們現在不在家
SHANE: Thanks for calling the Conroys. We're not home right now.
請在B聲後留言 謝謝
Please leave a message after the beep. Thanks!
我們很抱歉 你的電話沒有連接上 請重新撥打
We're sorry, your call cannot be completed. Please, dial again.
操
Shit.
-保羅? -這是他的號碼
-Dan: Paul? -Here's his number.
-請稍等 好的 繼續 -好 等等
-Hold on. All right, go ahead. -Okay. Hold on.
號碼是07-902-24-921.
It's 07-902-24-921.
好的數據很龐大 除非他們使用克隆電話
Okay. This is huge, Paul. Unless they're using a cloned line,
我們可以在幾分鐘內查到這是在哪裏撥出的電話
we should be able to find where this is coming from in minutes.
好的 我呢?你能追蹤到我的手機信號嗎?
Okay. What about me? Can you track my cell signal?
追蹤你的手機我們遇到很多麻煩
We 're having a lot of trouble with yours.
看起來像是EDS的線路
Seems to be an EDS line,
或許是通過埃及中轉的
probably through one of the Egyptian carriers.
什麼意思?
What does that mean?
-就是追蹤你的電話很難 -他要我拍一個索取贖金視頻
-That it's just not going to be easy. -He wants me to make a ransom video.
不 盡量拖延時間
No. Hold off for as long as you can.
如果這能讓我離開這裏 我會拍的
If it gets me out of here, I'm making it.
我們最不想見到的就是這個視頻在半島電視播放
The last thing we want is for this to end up all over Al Jazeera.
-我們? -是的
-We'? - Yes.
這個不能成為國際性事故
This can't turn into an international incident.
這就是你們在意的?你們在意我嗎?
That's all you people care about, isn't it? Don't you care about me?
-我們當然在意 -我呢?
-We do. -What about me?
我們真的在意你 保羅 這就是我為什麼在這裏的原因
We do, Paul, we do. That's why we're here.
不 不 不 你們不在乎我
No, no, no, you don't! You don't care about me.
你不在乎我們任何人
You don't care about any of us.
我有8個朋友在外面被殺了 今天就死了6個
I've had eight friends killed out here, six of them today.
-聽著 保羅 -我們沒有槍 沒有武裝
-Listen, Paul. You just... -We don't have any guns, any armor.
-什麼都沒有 -那是因為你們不是軍人
-Nothing. -That's because you're not soldiers.
這話你去跟那些把我困在這裏的人
Tell that to the people who put me in this box!
-保羅 聽著 -去跟那些殺了我朋友的人說
-Paul, listen. -Tell that to the people who shot my friends!
-我們在盡最大的努力 -不 你們沒有
-We're doing the best we can. -No, you're not! You're not!
-請冷靜一點 -我來這裏9個月了
-Okay, calm down. -I've been out here nine months.
我知道的 你們這些人僅僅在乎
I know how it works. All you guys care about
你們的秘密計劃和後門政策
is your secret plans and your back-room politics.
你知道 如果我是一個外交官
You know, if I was a diplomat,
或者是人質解救小組的領導 或者哪個單位的領導
or a hostage working group leader, or what the fuck your title is,
我早就出去了
I'd be out of here by now.
但我不是 所以我只有坐在這裏 閉上我的嘴等死
But I'm not, so I'm just supposed to sit in here, shut my mouth and die.
我需要你注意力集中一點 保羅
Okay, I need you to stay focused, Paul.
草泥馬 丹
Fuck you, Dan.
保羅 聽我說 找到你是我們的首要大事
Paul, listen to me. Finding you is our primary concern.
底線是 找你就像
Bottom line. And we 're searching for you
找四星上將一樣努力
just as hard as we would be for a four-star general,
所以我建議你不要在浪費力氣了
so don't literally waste your breath suggesting otherwise.
我不能...我不能...
I can't... I can't...
你受傷了嗎 保羅 你還好嗎
Are you injured, Paul? Are you okay?
我不知道  他們是誰
I don't know. Who are they?
那些把我困在這裏的人是誰
The people who put me in here, who are they?
他們只是人 跟你我沒什麼區別
They're just that, people. No different from you and me.
-我不是一個恐怖分子 -他們也不是
-I'm not a terrorist. -Neither are they.
你怎麼知道
How do you know?
如果你也是無家可歸 挨餓...我收回那句話
If you were homeless, starving... Actually I take that back.
如果你的家庭買不起房  挨餓 你會為了他們做什麼
If your family was homeless and starving, what would you do for them?
-我不會殺人 -你怎麼能這麼肯定?
-I wouldn't kill somebody. -How can you be sure?
有區別嗎
What difference does it make?
他們是孤注一擲的罪犯
They're criminals, desperate ones at that.
除了錢 他們什麼都不在乎
They don't care about anything other than getting the money.
所以付錢 付給他們錢
So pay them, just pay them.
相信我 如果可以這麼做 我會毫不猶豫的給錢
Trust me, if it was an option, I would do that in a heartbeat.
有多少人曾經被綁架?
How many others have there been?
-自從我到這裏? -是的
-Since I got here? -Yeah.
很多 記者  合同商  軍人
Dozens. Journalists, contractors, soldiers.
一堆人曾經被綁架 這是這裏唯一正常運轉的生意
Dozens have been taken. it's one of the only functioning businesses out here.
你救回了多少人
How many have you rescued?
-多少  -不多
-How many? -Not many.
-告訴我他們的名字 -不
-Tell me their names. -No.
-誰都行 -誰
-Any of them. -Who?
讓我相信你真的在乎他們
Make me believe that they really do matter to you.
真的真的在乎他們
That they really do matter to you.
-馬克 懷特 -誰是馬克 懷特
-Mark White. -Who was Mark White?
一個來自新漢普頓26歲的學生
A kid from New Hampshire. Twenty-six years old. Med student.
來這裏幫助當地醫生
Came over here to help out local doctors.
他怎樣了
What happened to him?
-叛亂者抓了他 -什麼時候
-Insurgents grabbed him. -When?
2個星期以前
About three weeks ago.
你記的住他們的名字?
You remember his name?
我記得他們所有人的名字
I remember all their names.
他還...
Is he... Did he?
是的 他還活著
Yeah. Yeah, he's alive.
-他現在在哪裏  -家裏
-Where is he now? -Home.
或許很高興的返回學校
Probably happy to be back at school.
我想離開這裏
I want to get out of here.
我們找到了他 我們也能找到你
We found him. We抣l find you, too.
怎樣找?
How?
通過你給我們的號碼我們已經有了確切的線索
We already have a solid lead on the number you gave us.
-你有? -是的 一支隊伍已經趕往過去了
-You do? -Yeah. A unit's on its way over there now.
太好了
That's good.
-感覺很好 -是啊
-That feels good. -Yeah.
那我現在應該幹什麼
What... What should I do in the meantime?
我知道很困難 但是請盡量放鬆
I know it's hard, but try to relax.
你越掙扎 你就會用掉越多的氧氣
The more worked up you are, the more air you're going to use.
好的 我知道了
Okay, I know.
我知道這很困難 因為我有焦慮癥
I know. it's hard, 'cause I have anxiety.
我必須吃藥
I take pills for it.
-你身上有藥嗎?  -有
-Do you have them with you? -Yeah.
很好 那就吃吧
Good. Take them.
你必須用盡一切辦法來維持你的氧氣水平
You need to preserve your oxygen level any way you can.
好的
Okay.
-你的打火機還點著嗎?  -沒有
-ls your Zippo still lit? -No, not anymore.
-很好 -我感覺想嘔
-All right. Good. -I feel nauseous.
-你需要冷靜下來 -好的
-You have to calm down. -Okay.
還有你需要節約電量
And you need to save that battery.
我們期待10分鐘內會有消息進來
We 're expecting some intel in about 10 minutes.
-到時打給我  -好的
-Call me back then. -Okay.
-堅持住 保羅  -我盡力
-Just hang in there, Paul. - I'm trying, okay.
-什麼? -你拍視頻?
-What? -JABIR: You make video?
-不 -你拍視頻
-No. -You make video!
-讓我出去我就拍 -不
-Let me out and I'll make it. -No!
-你現在就拍 -我看不到紙條
-You make video now. -I can't read the paper.
-馬上拍視頻 -我不能
-Make video now! -I can't.
我不知道你要我說什麼 我看不到紙條
I don't know what you want me to say. I can't read the paper.
你 馬上拍視頻
You make video! Now!
我操
I Fuck!
好 好 快 快
Okay, okay. Come on, come on, come on.
快
Come on!
快啊 快啊 快啊
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
我操
Fuck.
Shit.
山景醫院
NURSE: Mountain View Nursing Home.
我希望能跟瑪麗 康羅伊通電話
Hi. I was hoping that I could speak with Maryanne Conroy, please.
好的
Okay.
我把電話拿給她 請稍等
Let me bring the cordless phone to her room. Hold on one moment, please.
康羅伊太太 有電話找你
Mrs. Conroy, you have e telephone cell, dean
給你 你能用這個接聽
Here, you can use this phone.
喂
Hello?
媽 我是保羅
Mom it's Paul
誰
Who?
保羅 你的兒子
It's Paul, your son.
我有兒子?
I have a son?
沒關係 媽媽 你怎樣了
It's okay, Mom. How are you?
-我很好 -那就好
-I'm fine. -That's good.
你是誰
Who are you?
我是你的兒子 媽媽 我是小保羅
It's your son, Mom. It's Paulie.
-小保羅 -是的
-Paulie. -Yeah .
記得了嗎?曾經住在科法大街  你記得了嗎
Remember? Used to live on Colfax Street, in the duplex. You remember?
-小保羅 -嗯
-Paulie? -Yeah .
-沒錯 -是小保羅嗎?
-That's right. -ls this Paulie?
我是小保羅
It is. Its Paulie.
-家裏怎樣了 -很好
-How's everything at the home? -Very nice.
你爸爸和我每晚都玩琴酒紙牌遊戲
Your father and I have been playing Gin Rummy every night.
嗯
Yeah.
我不認為爸爸跟你在一起 媽媽
I don't think Pop's there with you, Mom.
你怎樣了 親愛的
How are you doing, sweetie?
不是很好
Not very good.
這可能是我最後一次跟你談話了
This might be the last time that I talk to you.
很好 寶貝
That's nice, honey.
你收到我幾個月前送的花了嗎
Did you get the flowers I sent you a few months ago?
-花? -是的 我送你的 無所謂了
-Flowers? -Yeah, I sent you... Never mind.
我現在要掛了 好嗎
Look, I'm gonna get going now, okay?
我晚點再打給你
I just wanted to call and talk to you.
我愛你 媽媽
I love you, Mom.
我說 我愛你 你要跟我說你愛我嗎
I said, I love you, Mom. Do you want to tell me that you love me?
是的 你爸爸每晚都跟我玩琴酒紙牌
Yes, dear Your father and I have been playing Gin Rummy every night.
好的 媽媽
Okay, Mom.
你代我跟爸爸問好
You tell Pop I said hi.
不
No.
不 不 不 不
No,no,no,no,no!
No,no,no,no,no,no!
-視頻拍了嗎?  -求求你 別傷害她
-JABIR: Video make? -Please! Don't hurt her!
-別傷害她 讓她走 -你不拍視頻 我就殺了她
-Don't hurt her! Let her go. -I shoot if you no make video.
-不 不 不要殺她 -你給我錢 要美金
-No! No! Don't shoot her. Don't shoot. -You get money. American million.
我會的 我保證
I will. I will! I promise.
我保證 求求你了 她是一個母親 她有2個孩子
I promise. Please, she's a mother. She has two kids.
-2個孩子? -是的 她有2個孩子
-Two kids? -Yes. She has two kids.
我有5個孩子 但是現在只剩下1個
I had five. Now only one.
-你馬上拍視頻  -等等
-You make video now! -Wait! Wait!
-不 等等 -我給你三秒
-No, wait! -I give three seconds.
-我不知道你要我說什麼  -3..
-I don't know what you want me to say! -Three...
-好 好 好 我拍視頻 - 2.. 1..
-Okay! Okay! I'll make the video! -Two, one!
我會拍視頻 求求你
I'll make the video! I'll make the video! Please, please, please.
我現在掛掉電話馬上拍視頻 好嗎
I have to hang up now to make the video. Is that okay?
你有3分鐘來發送視頻
You have three minute to send video.
我的名字叫保羅 康羅伊
My name is Paul Conroy.
我是來自密歇根州哈斯廷斯的美國公民
I'm an American citizen from Hastings, Michigan.
我是一個為CRT工作的平民司機
I'm a civilian truck driver for Crestin, Roland and Thomas.
現在我在伊拉克被綁架
And I have been taken hostage somewhere in Iraq.
巴格達時間今晚9點錢我需要1百萬美金
I need $1 million by 9:00 tonight, Baghdad time,
否則我會被埋在一個棺材裏被撕票
or I'll be left to die here in this coffin that I'm buried in.
我被告知如果付錢了
I'm told that if the money is paid...
我被告知如果付錢了  他們會放我走
I'm told that if the money is paid, I will be let go.
如果沒有 我就會在這裏死去
If it is not, I will be left to die here.
以上所述都是真實的
These threats are real and will be followed through on.
天啊
Oh, my God.
找到你了
I got you.
找到你了 狗娘樣的
I got you, you motherfucker.
找到你了 找到你了 找到你了
I got you. I got you. I got you. I got you.
狗樣的
Fucking A. Okay.
快 快 快 接電話
Come on, come on, come on. Pick up, pick up, pick up, pick up, pick up.
你好 我是琳達 請留下口信
Hi, this is Linda. Please leave a message.
祝你有愉快的一天
Thanks and have a great day.
琳達 我找到電話號碼了 我找到了
Linda, I figured out the number of the phone. I got it.
我找到了
I got it!
號碼是0792-42-884.
Okay. It's 0792-42-884.
打國際電話 記得加代碼
Use the international calling code to dial it. I got it, baby.
我愛你 收到馬上打電話給我
I love you. Call me as soon as you get this. Call me. I love you.
我操
Oh, shit.
Shit.
好
Okay.
我操 快
Fuck. Come on.
我操
Fuck.
我的名字是帕梅拉 拉蒂
My name is Pamela Lutti.
我是CRT公司旗下
I'm a food service worker at FOB Anaconda,
的員工
employed by Crestin, Roland and Thomas.
抓我的人都要求沒有被滿足
My captors' requests have gone unanswered.
求求你 求求你 不要
Please. Please, don't!
我的名字是帕梅拉 拉蒂
My name is Pamela Lutti.
求求你了 不要
Please, don't!
如果你被埋在了棺材裏面  那麼你從哪裏打電話來?
If you're buried in a coffin, where are you calling from?
你撥打的電話
The number you requested,
269-948-1998.
他們是孤注一擲的罪犯
They're criminals, desperate ones at that.
除了錢  他們什麼都不在乎
They don't care about anything other than getting...
在CRT公司  我們與顧客....
At CRT, we work with our clients to provide...
請不要大喊大叫....
HARRIS: Sin you're gonna have to stop shouting.
今晚9點前給我五百萬 否則你就留在這裏
JABIR: Five million, money tonight, 9:00 p. m., or you stay.
找到你是目前最緊急的事
DAN: Finding you is our primary concern. Bottom line.
感謝致電康羅伊一家 我們目前不在家
SHANE: Thanks for calling the Conroys. We're not home right now.
請在B一聲後留言 謝謝
Please, leave a message after the beep. Thanks!
為什麼你要拍那個視頻
DAN: Why the hell did you make that video?
-全都是一堆謊言 -什麼?
-It's all a bunch of lies. -What is?
你在說什麼
What are you talking about?
-全部 -什麼全部
-All Of it. -All Of What?
你根本就不在乎我們 我們對你們來說是個屁
You don't give a shit about any of us. We're nothing to you people.
我們會找到你的
We're going to find you.I
滾開 丹 你以為你是保姆嗎
Fuck off, Dan. You're babysitting.
你就陪我講電話直到我死去吧
Just gonna stay on the phone with me until I die.
你不能放棄啊 保羅
Okay. You can't start breaking on me now, Paul.
-你要堅強  -他們殺了她而你們什麼都沒做
-You have to stay strong. -They shot her and you didn't do anything.
我們不知道她被綁架了
We didn't even know she'd been taken hostage.
-她發了三段視頻 -是的  那是他們逼她這麼說的
-She sent three videos. -Yeah. That's what they told her to say.
-為什麼 -我不知道
-Why? -I don't know.
你知道什麼
What do you know?
你的要求贖金視頻在youtube上
That your ransom video already has
已經被點擊了47  000次了
47,000 hits on YouTube.
所有主流媒體包括半島電視台都在播放那個片段
And all the major networks are playing it, including Al Jazeera.
所以現在綁匪沒有選擇只能繼續堅持下去
So now your captors have no choice but to follow through.
我找到這台手機的號碼了
I found out the number to this phone.
-怎麼找的?  -誰在意?
-How? -Who cares?
我找到了 而你沒有找到 這是為什麼
I figured it out and you didn't. Why?
因為我沒有
Because I didn't.
就像你和其他在這個星球上的人
Just like you and every other person on the planet,
有些事我知道 有些事我不知道
there are some things I know, and there are some things I don't.
那我是不是永遠都出不去了?
Then how am I ever gonna get out of here?
正如我預料的 他們的信號是克隆的 我們就快找到了
Their signal was cloned, like we figured. But we're close. Really close.
我在一個清真寺附近
I'm near a mosque.
我聽到了擴音機上的祈禱文
I heard a call to prayer over the PA.
很好 那意味著我們在正確的區域內
Good. Good. That means that we're in the right area.
你在....
You're...
你在附近?
You're nearby?
我跟護送你們車隊的士兵談過
I spoke with soldiers from the 3rd ID who were escorting your convoy.
他們還活著?
They're alive?
不是全部 基本都被路邊的簡易炸彈炸傷了
Not all of them. Both Bradley tanks were hit with IEDs.
其餘的被一些流彈擊傷
The rest got caught in small arms fire
到底發生了什麼 保羅
What the hell happened out there, Paul?
保羅
Paul?
等等
Wait.
保羅
Paul?
我操
FUCK!
快 快
Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
快
Come on.
喂
Hello?
喂 誰在那裏?是保羅 康羅伊嗎
Hello, who's there? ALAN: ls this Paul Conroy?
是的 我是保羅 你是誰
Yeah, yeah, yeah. it's Paul. Who are you?
保羅 我是阿蘭 達文普
Paul, my name 's Alan Davenport.
我是CRT公司的人事部主管
I'm the Personnel Director here at Crestin, Roland and Thomas.
嗯  我給你留了口信
Yeah, yeah. I left you a message.
是的 我也從政府部門的麗貝卡 布朗寧那裏聽說了
You did. I also heard from Rebecca Browning over at the State Department.
你現在的狀況可以說話嗎
Are you able to speak on the status of your situation?
更糟了 剛才好像有場爆炸 現在沙子開始灌進來了
It's worse. There was an explosion or something, and the sand's coming through.
估計還有半小時就能灌滿這裏了
I probably have about half an hour before it fills right up.
你應該嘗試冷靜下來
Slow down. You should try to stay calm.
那個綁匪 丹 布倫娜來自人質解救小組
The hostage-takers, Dan Brenner from the hostage working group...
好的 保羅 那些媒體怎樣了?
Okay, Paul. I'm with you. Now, how about the media?
我知道你的贖金視頻洩露了
I know your ransom video leaked,
但是你有跟其他人直接溝通過這件事嗎
but have you spoken directly to anyone about what's going on?
-沒有 沒有  -很好 很好
-No. No, no, no, no. -Good, good, good, good.
你必須這樣
It needs to stay that way.
把情況控制好是非常重要的
It's important we keep this situation as contained as possible.
目前的情況是我在一個棺材裏
The situation is in a coffin!
我想這控制的非常好 救我 救我
I think it's pretty contained! Help me! Help me!
你正在做什麼來救我
What are you doing right now to help me?
我知道你很沮喪 但是我被告知
I know you're upset. But from what I've been told,
他們距離你已經很近了
they're extremely close to getting you out of there.
所以希望不會太長時間
So hopefully it won't be too much longer
-謝謝上帝 -是啊 謝謝上帝
-Thank God. -Yeah, thank God.
現在 我要打開錄音機
Now, I'm going to switch on a recorder right now.
-什麼?  -等等
-What? -Just a second.
我是阿蘭 達文普
This is Alan Davenport,
克裏斯汀 羅蘭 湯瑪士公司的人事部主管
Personnel Director at Crestin, Roland and Thomas Incorporated.
今天是2006年10月23日
The date is October 23, 2006.
我正在和保羅 康羅伊講話
I'm speaking with Paul Conroy.
康羅伊先生 我在錄這段話的時候你是否清醒?
Mr Conroy are you aware that I'm recording this conversation?
-什麼?  -請回答這個問題
-What? -Please answer the question.
-操  -康羅伊先生
-Shit. -Mn Conroy?
嗯 嗯
Yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah.
我有得到你的允許嗎?
And do I have your permission to do so?
你為什麼需要我的許可?你到底在說什麼
Why do you need my permission? What's this about?
我需要回答 有還是沒有
I need you to answer yes or no, please.
-有 有 滿意嗎? -謝謝
-Yes! Yes, all right? -Thank you.
康羅伊先生 你幾時受雇於CRT公司?
Now, Mr Conroy, when were you hired by CRT?
我不..9個月以前 大概在1月 到底怎麼了
I don't... Nine months ago. Around January. What is all this?
我這裏的官方記錄顯示你受雇於1月4號
I have your official date of hire as January 4th.
-正確嗎?  -誰在意?
-ls that correct? -Who cares?
這真他媽的神經病
This is fucking crazy.
-1月4號 正確嗎  -正確
-January 4th. ls that correct? -Yes!
在你的前期訓練中  在被派遣到伊拉克前
And during your initial training, before being sent to Iraq,
你已經意識到了你所在的職位要承擔的風險
you were made aware of the dangers inherent to the position for which you were hired.
你指的是我去達拉斯時你們承諾的所有卡車
You mean when I came down there to Dallas, and you guys said that all of the trucks
都有武裝和防彈玻璃?
would be armored and have bulletproof glass?
你指的是你告訴我們這個比任何時候都安全?
You mean when you told us that things were safer than ever over here?
是那個時候..是那個時候我意識到的嗎?
Is that when... Is that when I was made aware?
我需要你回答 是還是不是
I need you to answer yes or no, please.
是
Yes.
在那個時候 你是否也收到和CRT
During that time, did you also receive and sign an employment contract with CRT,
簽署了詳細說明公司政策
which thoroughly explained company policy
和包含了特定條款的就業合同
as it pertained to your specific terms of employment?
是 是 是 我簽了一堆東西
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I signed a bunch of things. Yeah.
-是還是不是?  -是 我簽了合同
-Yes or no? -Yes! I signed the contract. Yes.
我們也知道了2小時以前
It's our understanding that you were taken hostage in Iraq
你在伊拉克被劫持為人質  正確嗎?
two hours ago, is that also correct?
是 我認為那是對目前狀況相當客觀的評價 你個大屌哥
Yes! I think that's a fair assessment of the situation, you fucking dick.
這些有什麼意義?
What's the point of all this?
我們的法律部門要求要一份員工宣誓過的證詞
Our legal department requires that we obtain a sworn affidavit from employees,
來證明他們明白公司必須強制解除合同的原因
confirming that they understand the reasons for their forced separation from the company.
從今天早上起 你和CRT公司的合同已經被取消了
As of this morning, your employment with CRT was officially terminated.
等等 等等 你說什麼?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What?
我們注意到你和一位
It was brought to our attention that you were engaging
前CRT員工帕梅拉 拉蒂有關係
in relations with a fellow CRT employee, Pamela Lutti.
-不 不 不 等等 -你的合同有
-No. No, no. Hold on, hold on. -Stipulated in your contract
交友條款 裏面說的很清楚
was a fraternization clause, in which it was stated quite clearly
-任何....   - 等等 請等等
-that any relationship... -Stop, stop, stop. Please.
戀愛還是性關係...
...be it romantic or sexual in nature...
-我們只是朋友  -被認為是不恰當的
-We were just friends. -. . . deemed inappropriate
CRT有權立即終止合同關係
by CRT senior officials is grounds for immediate termination.
等等 好嗎  我們只是朋友
Hold on. Okay? We were just friends. We were just friends.
-我們的記錄可不是這樣 -你的記錄是錯的
-Our records indicate differently. -Your records are wrong.
我們也正式通知你
We 're also legally required to inform you
因為你從法律上來說
that because you were technically no longer
在你被綁架時你已經不是CRT的員工
under the employ of CRT at the time of your abduction,
所以我們不會負責解雇你後
we cannot be held accountable for any injury
在你身上受到的任何傷害
that may befall upon you after your official date and time of termination.
因此 在你的案件中 包括這次事故
Therefore, in your case, that includes this incident,
還有這次事故導致的任何後果
or any consequences that may result from it.
那我的保險金呢 我家人需要那筆錢
What about my insurance money? My family's gonna need that money.
由於你的合同已經被終止.....
Given that you were alive up until the time of your termination...
不要這樣
Don't do this.
-你明白這些嗎?  -不要這樣做
-Do you understand everything? -Don't do this!
你明白我跟你說的嗎 康羅伊先生
Do you understand everything you've been told, Mn Conroy?
康羅伊先生
Mn Conroy?
你就是個狗屎
You're a piece of shit.
和保羅 康羅伊的談話到底結束
That concludes our interview with Paul Conroy.
我現在關閉錄音機
I am now turning off the recorder
你把我放在這裏
You put me here.
對不起
I'm sorry.
接電話 接電話
Answer the phone. Answer the phone.
快 為什麼你不接電話
Come on. Why won't you answer the phone?
保羅 是你嗎
DAN: Paul, is that you?
他們都死了
They're dead.
-你怎麼知道? -我就是知道
-How do you know that? -I just do.
3架F16剛才城市上空盤旋
Three F-16s leveled parts of the city a few minutes ago.
嗯 我知道
Yeah, I know.
嗯 那很有趣
Yeah, that was fun for me.
他們知道我在這裏嗎
Did they know I was here?
-是的  -嗯
-Yeah. -Yeah.
他們在意嗎
Did they care?
這些綁匪 如果他們死了
These people that took me, if they're dead,
他們就不能告訴你我在哪
they can't tell you where I am.
我們仍然可以追蹤你的信號
We can still try to track down your signal.
你已經試過了
You tried that already.
我們可以再試一次
We can try again.
-都結束了是吧  -不
-It's over, isn't it? -No.
是的
Yeah.
我應該怎麼辦
What should I do?
我不知道
I don't know.
好奇怪
It's weird.
什麼
What is
先知
Knowing.
我希望結果會不一樣 保羅
I wish this could have gone differently Paul.
是啊
Yeah.
我也想
Me, too.
我的名字是保羅 斯蒂芬 康羅伊
My name is Paul Steven Conroy.
社保號是048321198 生日是3/23/76.
Social security number, 048-32-1198. Date of birth. 3/23/76.
這段視頻是我的最後心願和遺囑
This video will serve as my last will and testament.
給我的妻子 琳達 康羅伊
To my wife, Linda Conroy,
我給你留下了700美金在我的個人存款裏
I leave you the $700 in my personal savings,
還有剩下的養老金
and whatever's left in my annuity.
給我的兒子 沙恩 康羅伊
To my son, Shane Conroy,
我不知道
I don't know
我沒有...我的衣服
I don't have... My clothes.
我給你我的衣服 你會長大的
I leave you my clothes, which you will grow into.
不是這些
Not these ones.
我真的沒有....
I don't really have...
我希望我能留下更多給 但是...
I wish that I had more for you, but...
如果我是著名的壁球運動員 或者穿著西裝上班的人
Maybe if I was a famous baseball player, or some guy who wore a suit to work...
那樣我會擁有更多
Then I'd have more.
但是 你懂的 你能成為那類型的人
But, you know, you can be one of those people if you want. Um...
是啊
Yeah. Yeah.
答應我你長大後你會好好照顧母親
Just promise me that when you get older that you'll take good care of your mom.
嗯 我不知道
And, I don't know.
你總是嘗試做些正確的事
You always try to do the right thing.
我非常愛你 沙恩
I love you very much, Shane.
或許我說的不夠 或許夠 我不知道
Maybe I never said that enough. Maybe I did. I don't know.
那或許意味著不夠
That probably means I didn't. And...
對不起 琳達 我應該聽你的
I'm sorry, Linda. I should have listened to you.
你還沒有死 喂 喂
You're not dead. Hello? Hello?
錢呢?
JABIR: Where is money?
-我不知道 -什麼不知道
-I don't know. -What don't know?
-我不知道在哪裏 -騙子
-I don't know where it is. -Liar!
我發誓我沒說謊
No, I'm not lying! I swear.
-你發誓? -嗯 我發誓
-Swear? -Yeah, I swear.
-我說的實話 -從大使館拿
-I'm telling the truth. -From embassy.
-不 -你現在有錢了?
-No. -You get money now!
-我不能夠 -你會的
-I can't! -You will!
-我需要多點時間 -沒有時間了
-I need more time. Please. -No more time!
沙子正在漏下來
There's sand pouring in here.
到處都是 讓我出去 我保證我會給錢你
It's everywhere. Let me out of here, and I promise you I will get you the money.
-你流血 -什麼
-You show blood. -What?
-你流血了 他們就給錢 -不
-You show blood, they give money. -No.
你切掉手指 拍視頻
You cut finger; send video.
-不 我不會那麼做的 -你會的
-No, I'm not doing that. -Yes!
-不 -不?
-No. -No?
不 我不會幹的 你讓我出去
No, that's right, no. You let me out of here,
我會完整無缺的出去
and I'll out off my whole goddamn hand if you want.
-你有妻子?  -是的
-You have wife? -Yeah, I do.
我還有個年幼的兒子 我還想見到他 求你了 大哥
And a son. I have a young son. And I want to see them again. Please, sir.
-大哥? -是的 大哥
-Sir? -Yes. Sir.
我充滿尊敬的叫你大哥
I say that out of respect to you.
美國密歇根州哈斯廷斯北胡桃林街243號
243, North Walnut Street. Hastings, Michigan, USA.
那是我的...你為什麼說那個
That's my... Why did you say that?
你流血還是他們流血
You show blood, or they show blood.
你們什麼都不是
No. You're nobody, all of you.
你接近不了他們
You can't get to them.
-不?  -不
-No? -No.
你就是個農夫 就是個罪犯
You're peasants. You're fucking criminals, that's all.
你連密歇根在哪裏都不知道
You don't even know where Michigan is.
底特律 安娜堡
Detroit. Ann Arbor
你在看地圖 你在看地圖
You looked at a map. You looked at a map.
你流血還是他們流血 5分鐘內發送視頻過來
You show blood, or they show blood. Send video by five minutes.
你好  我是琳達請留言謝謝並祝你度過愉快的一天
Hi, this is Linda. Please leave a message. Thanks and have a great day.
琳達!琳達  聽我說  你和謝恩必須去某處  好嗎?
Linda! Linda, listen to me, you and Shane have to go somewhere, okay?
不要回家  不要回家
Do not go back to the house. Do not go back to the house.
去哪裏都好就是不要回家好嗎?他們知道我們住在哪裏
Just go anywhere but to the house. Okay? These guys, they know where we live.
他們有我的駕照
They have my driver's license.
逼不得已你就去警察局  就是別回家
Just go to the sheriff's station if you have to, just do not go home.
天啊
Holy God.
操
Fuck.
這是丹尼爾布倫納請留言
This is Daniel Brenner Please leave a message at the tone.
布倫納  你在哪裏?那些傢伙仍然活著!
Brenner, where are you? The guy's still alive!
他剛打電話給我  他還活著
He just called me. He's still alive.
操
Fuck.
他們找不到他們
They can't find them. They can't.
沒門不  不  不
There's no way. No, no, no, no, no.
他們找不到他們  他們找不到他們
They can't find them. They can't find them. They can't find them.
操
Fuck.
我叫帕梅拉 拉蒂
My name is Pamela Lutti.
我是一個餐館服務員
I'm a food service worker at FOB Anaconda,
受雇於CRT公司
employed by Crestin, Roland and Thomas. (CRYING)
抓我的人的要求得不到答覆
My captors' requests have gone unanswered.
求你了  不要
Please. Please, don't!
操
Fuck.
-繞到那邊去  -快 行動
-Around to the other side! -Move it, move it, move it!
我看見他了!!
MAN 1. I see him! Move it!I
回來  大家快回來!
Get back! Everybody, get back!
平民已經找到了  平民已經找到了
Civilian has been located. Civilian has been located.
你還好嗎?跟我說話
MAN 3: Are you okay? Talk to me.
保羅  你還好嗎?
Paul, are you okay?
什麼?
Yeah?
保羅?保羅  我是布倫納
Paul? Paul, it's Brenner.
-你在那裏嗎保羅? -我在這兒?
-Are you there, Paul? -I'm here?
我們現在來救你了你聽到沒?我們找到你了
We 're coming for you now. You hear me? We know where you are.
你們救我來了?-是的  保羅
-You're coming? -We are, Paul.
-我們就在附近了-你怎麼知道?
-We 're almost there now. -How do you know?
聯軍們在巴格達外面抓到了一個反叛者
Coalition forces picked up a Shi'ite insurgent just outside of Baghdad.
說他知道一個美國人在哪裏被活埋的
Said he knew where an American was buried alive.
他同意如果我們放他走他就告訴我們在哪裏
He agreed to show us where if we let him go.
-你們救我來了?-事實上我們已經到了
-You're coming for me? -We are practically there already.
-你必須...你必須快點-我們很快了  保羅
-You have... You have to hurry. -We are, Paul.
你們必須快點沙子...沙子...
You have to hurry. The sand... The sand...
你只要在那堅持多三分鐘
You just hang in there three more minutes.
這一切就要結束了我發誓  保羅
This will all be over soon, I promise, Paul.
好  好我相信你
Okay. Okay. I believe you.
三分鐘  保羅我只需要你再堅持三分鐘
Three minutes, Paul. I just need you to hang on for three minutes.
-謝謝-這一切就要結束了  我答應你...
-Thank you. -This will all be over soon. I promise you...
-我得走了!打回給我-不  不!保羅  保羅  保羅!
-I have to go! Call me right back. -No, no, no! Paul, Paul, Paul!
-請給我回電!-不  等等  保羅!
-Call me right back. Please! -No, wait, Paul!
琳達!琳達!
Linda! Linda!
保羅?保羅  是你嗎?
Paul? Paul, is that you?
-告訴我那是你 -是我
-Tell me it's you. - It's me.
噢  我的天  保羅!他們對你做了什麼?
Oh, my God, Paul! What are they doing to you?
-請告訴我你沒事-我很好
-Please tell me you're okay. -I'm okay.
我剛剛看了新聞我把手機忘在家裏了
I just saw the news. I left my cell phone at home.
他們知道我在哪裏他們正要來抓我
They know where I am. They're coming to get me.
那些美國人來救我了
The Americans are coming for me.
-是嗎?  -會沒事的
-They are? -it's going to be okay.
謝天謝地
Thank God. Thank God.
他們就要來了  他們正在路上  一切會好的
They're coming. They're on their way. it's gonna be okay.
我多麼害怕就要失去你
I was so afraid I was going to lose you.
-不會的   -我多麼愛你
-You're not. -I love you so much.
-我多麼愛你  -我多麼愛你
-I love you so much. -I love you so much.
我多麼愛你  很抱歉  我本不應該來的
I love you so much. I'm so sorry. I should never have come here.
我本應該聽你的話  對不起
I should have listened to you. I'm sorry.
親愛的  我不管了我只想你回家  回到我身邊
Sweetie, I don't care. I just want you home. Please come home to me.
我會回家的  我會回家
I'm coming home. I'm coming home.
-你發誓   -我發誓
-Swear it. -I swear.
-我發誓我會回家   -我愛你  我深深地愛著你
-I swear I'm coming home. -I love you. I love you so much.
我知道
I know.
-他們在這裏   -好的
-They're here. -Okay.
他們在這裏!我必須走了
They're here! I have to go.
-馬上打給我-我會的  我答應你
-Call me right away. -I will. I promise you
-我會的我愛你   -我愛你你發誓
-I will. I love you. -I love you. Swear it.
-我很愛你   -再次發誓
-I love you so much. -Swear it again.
我發誓!我得走了
I swear! I have to go.
-請回到我身邊   -我愛你
-Please come home to me. -I love you.
-丹?  -快!快!我們走!
-Dan?  -Move! Move! Let's go!
-布倫娜?   -好的保羅?保羅?我們在這兒!
-Brenner? -Okay Paul? Paul? We're here!
-是我    -他把我們帶到你這兒來了
-it's me. -He brought us right to you.
快  快你必須快點它就快滿了
Hurry, hurry. You have to hurry. It's almost full. Please.
保羅  在那堅持一下我們就在你上面
Paul, just hang in there. We're right above you.
我不能  我不能堅持了你們在附近?
I can't. I can't. Are you close?
-我們就差不多在那了!-你們在不遠處?
-We 're almost there! -Are you close?
我們就差不多在那裏了!正上方!
We 're almost there! Right above!
-求求你!我聽不到你說什麼!   -繼續挖
-Please! Please! I can't hear you! -Keep digging!
-我聽不見你說什麼!你們在哪裏?   -我們就在那裏了!
-I can't hear you! Where are you? -We 're almost there!
-一直挖!我們看見棺材了   -是的  挖吧
-Keep digging! We see the coffin. -Yeah, dig in...
-堅持住!    -請打開它請打開它
-Hang in there! -Please open it. Please open it.
我們走!快!大伙再快一點  再快一點!
Let's go! Move! Faster guys, faster!
-快點!快!   -好的  明白!
-Hurry up! Hurry! -Okay, okay, clear!
請她媽的快點!
Fucking hurry! Please!
快!
Hurry!
噢  我的天
Oh, my God.
-什麼?什麼?  -噢  我的天
-What? What? -Oh, my God.
-對不起保羅我很抱歉   -那是什麼...什麼?
-I'm so sorry Paul. I'm so sorry. -What is... What?
那是馬克懷特
It's Mark White.
他把我們帶到了馬克懷特身邊
He brought us to Mark White.
噢  天啊噢  天
Oh, God. Oh, God
-我很抱歉我很抱歉-好的
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry. -Okay.
好的噢  天啊!
Okay. Oh, God.
我很抱歉  保羅  真的很抱歉
I'm sorry Paul. I'm so sorry.